## Travis Umbel, Junior Web Developer

Madison, United States, 262-492-5905, Umbelth94@gmail.com

PROFILE

I am an upbeat, highly motivated worker with a diverse background and skillset. Mostly self-taught web developer with 2 years of experience able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Jul 2022 - Present

### Packaging Specialist, Octopi Brewing

Waunakee, WI

- · Operate machines and troubleshoot issues to ensure maximum production efficiency on the line
- Maintain quality product standards by routinely monitoring equipment and products
- · Changeover machines to various packaging types
- · Create and maintain SOP documentation
- Train new employees on efficient use of equipment and practices

Jan 2020 - May 2022

# Optics Technician, Pike Technologies

Fitchburg, WI

- Tested quality of IR Microscope objectives with a Zygo VFA (Asphere + Laser interface) Machine
- Inspected, cleaned, and packaged a variety of mirrors and lenses used in various FTIR (Fourier TransformInfrared) sampling machines
- Operated a vacuum coating machine to coat diamond lenses with Aluminum or Gold Adhesion
- · Interpreted diagrams for assembly of various parts

Jul 2019 - Jan 2020

### Wire Saw Technician, GE Healthcare

Milwaukee, WI

- Precise operation of Wire Saw to dice scintillator material, producing sensors for Computed Tomography (CT) applications
- · Observed & recorded in-process data, alerting Operations Engineering of process abnormalities
- Monitored equipment performance to support routine maintenance, ensuring process control

Aug 2017 - May 2019

#### Sales Associate, Menards

Burlington, WI

- Leadership role in a store remodel effort, team lead for the demolition and re-construction of shelving, pallet-racking, and new displays, as well as being in charge of organizing and storing the needed parts
- Temporary department manager for a new store set-up in charge of training new employees and teaching them SOP's for various tasks
- Created estimates for various guest projects, ensuring cost transparency & customer satisfaction
- Daily down-stocking/up-stocking
- · Responsible for condensing overstock pallets bi-weekly

#### EDUCATION

Dec 2023 - May 2024

### Certificate, UW Madison Online Bootcamp

Madison, WI

Currently enrolled in an online Full-Stack web development bootcamp that covers MERN stack development, Node.js, NoSQL, and Javascript with an emphasis on working collaboratively with others via Git, emphasizing Agile development strategies.

SKILLS React HTML5

jQuery JavaScript

CSS Git